caknowledge.in 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy - CAknowledge.com

## **Privacy Policy of CAknowledge.com**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form or comment on the site. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or website URL. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at raj302026@gmail.com.

At[ https://caknowledge.com/](https://caknowledge.com/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by https://caknowledge.com/ and how it is used.

At CAknowledge.in the  **privacy**  of our visitors is extremely important. This  _Privacy_  Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You will want to revisit it regularly. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

##  ** _1\. Log Files_**

We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:  
* Internet Protocol addresses (IP)  
* Types of browser  
* Internet Service Provider (ISP)  
* Date and time stamp  
* Referring and exit pages  
* Number of clicks  
All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

##  _ **2\. Cookies**_

We use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. In regard to third-party advertisers, All Blogging Tips has no access or control over these cookies. You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.  
If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites.

##  _ **3\. Other**_

Users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter by providing name and email address to receive communication from ABT. We use a secure op-in subscription system and we reserve the right to contact subscribers with information related to this website and blog. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime and every email delivered will contain an “Unsubscribe” link.

##  **Payment and Privacy Policy**

Our credit card payment method is highly secure as we do not keep credit card information related to the payment in our hands.

The whole credit card transaction is processed by [2CO](https://www.2checkout.com/) , a well known and secure credit card processing agent.

2CO processes orders on behalf of and have their own Privacy Policy which you should refer to. Any personal information received (like email) is for internal use only. We will  **not**  sell or redistribute your information to anyone.

We take your privacy seriously and will take all measures to protect your personal information.

##  **Refunds policy**

We want you to be satisfied with any product you buy from us, period. We generally don’t offer refunds for our products and services once you have made the payment and elected to continue with the product..

Please note that by purchasing the product or service, you agree to the terms of the Refund Policy.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy or refund policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [raj302026@gmail.com](mailto:raj302026@gmail.com)

##  **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will send an email notifying you of any changes.

##  **Contact Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

 **https://caknowledge.com**  
Raju Choudhary (Founder CAknowledge.com)  
[**raj302026@gmail.com**](mailto:raj302026@gmail.com) OR **admin@caknowledge.com**  
+918854810117
